http://www.fictionalfootball.co.uk/privacy

Skip to the content Betting NewsCasinosSportTips & Guides Search for:
Privacy PolicyYour privacy is important to us. It is our policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website.We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used.We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy policies.You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.CookiesThis website uses a service called Google Analytics in order to measure the number of visitors that use our site. Google Analytics uses a combination of cookies in order to provide this service. You can read Google’s cookie policy here. You can find instructions for removing cookies from your computer here.
Latest Betting News The Pros And Cons Of Playing Online Slots Online Slots That Payout Ridiculous Prizes Can You Safely Play Online Blackjack? The Best Premier League Imports Are online games entertainment or learning?Sports News Transfer rumours: White, Upamecano, Alaba, Garcia, Rojo, Eriksen, Szoboszlai Dundalk 2-4 Arsenal: Gunners finish Group B with 100% record Champions Cup - what you need to know Fifa president Gianni Infantino rejects 'baseless' private jet claims Joshua v Pulev: 'Tyson Fury questions can wait until after crucial fight'Horse Racing News Funding Boost For Scottish Racing A Wonderful Ride: A Tribute to Kenny LeJeune Irish Injured Jockeys Calendars, Christmas Cards On Sale HRI Awards To Be Shown On Racing TV Kentucky Sires for 2021, Part I: New Sires © 2020 Betting Gorilla. All rights reserved.Betting Gorilla HomepageLatest Gambling NewsCasino NewsSports NewsGambling Tips & GuidesAbout UsContactSupport & AdviceWrite For UsPrivacy PolicySitemapContact us: info@bettinggorilla.com
